{"id":"2018_9","name":"","memoryVerse":"\"Then Samuel took a stone and set it up between Mizpah and Shen. He named it Ebenezer, saying, 'Thus far the Lord has helped us.' \" â€“ 1 Samuel 7:12","dayQuestions":{"one":{"title":"FIRST DAY: Read the notes and the references.","questions":[{"id":"2018_9_1","questionText":"1. Use this space to record how you have seen God's activity during the week. (How has He provided, answered, comforted, reconciled, guided, etc.?)","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_9_2","questionText":"2. What from the notes, lecture, group sharing or personal study impacted you most in the past week?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"two":{"title":"SECOND DAY: Read 1 Samuel 9-10.\nGod directed Samuel to anoint and instruct Saul as Israel's first king.","readVerse":[{"book":"1 Samuel","verse":"9:1-10:999"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_9_3","questionText":"3. How did God reveal Saul was His choice for Israel's first king?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_9_4","questionText":"4. What signs and instructions did Samuel give Saul? What does this reveal about the king's relationship to God and His prophets?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_9_5","questionText":"5. What do you learn about God's call to a specific work? What is the work God has for you?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"three":{"title":"THIRD DAY: Read 1 Samuel 11.\nGod granted Saul and the Israelites victory over the Ammonites.","readVerse":[{"book":"1 Samuel","verse":"11:1-999"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_9_6","questionText":"6. What difficult situation did the people face? What seemingly impossible situation are you facing or have faced in the past?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_9_7","questionText":"7. What changes were evident in Saul when the Holy Spirit came upon him? (1 Samuel 10:22-26)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"1 Samuel","verse":"10:22-26"}]},{"id":"2018_9_8","questionText":"8. How has the Holy Spirit's indwelling changed and empowered you?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"four":{"title":"FOURTH DAY: Read 1 Samuel 12-13.\nSamuel instructed Israel to remember the Lord, but Saul ignored his instructions.","readVerse":[{"book":"1 Samuel","verse":"12:1-13:999"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_9_9","questionText":"9. In Samuel's farewell speech, what did he say about himself, God and the people?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_9_10","questionText":"10. How did the people respond? How did Samuel instruct and encourage them?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_9_11","questionText":"11. Why did Saul disobey Samuel's instructions? What were the consequences for Saul's disobedience? (1 Samuel 10:8)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"1 Samuel","verse":"10:8"}]},{"id":"2018_9_12","questionText":"12. What pressures to disobey do you face? How have you been impacted by your own or other's disobedience to God?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"five":{"title":"FIFTH DAY: Read 1 Samuel 14-15.\nSaul demonstrated unwise and ungodly leadership before God rejected him as king.","readVerse":[{"book":"1 Samuel","verse":"14:1-15:999"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_9_13","questionText":"13. How does Jonathan's courage and reliance on God in His battle against the Philistines inspire you? (1 Samuel 14:1-23)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"1 Samuel","verse":"14:1-23"}]},{"id":"2018_9_14","questionText":"14. What do the events in this battle reveal about Saul's character and leadership?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_9_15","questionText":"15. How did Saul excuse his disobedience? What excuses do you or others offer for your disobedience?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_9_16","questionText":"16. What do you learn about God through Saul's failures? How does this comfort or challenge you?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"six":{"title":"SIXTH DAY: Review 1 Samuel 9-15.","readVerse":[{"book":"1 Samuel","verse":"9:1-15:999"}],"questions":[{"id":"2018_9_17","questionText":"17. What was your biggest takeaway from your personal study of this week's lesson? from www.bsfinternational.org by class members, no portion of this material may be reproduced without written permission, according to copyright.)","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2018_9_18","questionText":"18. Homiletics for group and administrative leaders: 1 Samuel 9-15","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"1 Samuel","verse":"9:1-15:999"}]},{"id":"2018_9_18","questionText":"18. Homiletics for group and administrative leaders: 1 Samuel 9-15 People of the Promised Land I Lesson 9 \" www.bsfinternational.org AdQ (06.2018) \" 7 8 \" AdQ (06.2018) www.bsfinternational.org \" People of the Promised Land I Lesson 9","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"1 Samuel","verse":"9:1-15:999"}]}]}}}